[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Episode 10]
Why are you back?
I was about to ask you the same thing.
Didn't you say you went back home?
Why are you here alone?
Oh...
Well, my parents...
They decided to go on a trip at the last minute.
So, I came back early.
Did you spend the New Year all by yourself?
Is this what you ate last night?
Yeah.
Shen Mo.
Come here.
Didn't you say you were going to stay abroad for a few more days?
Why are you back so soon?
Something urgent came up.
I changed my plans.
What happened?
You know the answer.
How did you know that I didn't go back home...
and spent the New Year alone?
I realized it when I called last night.
It's a bit late now.
It's not late.
You rushed back...
It must have been hard to book a flight.
Those are all problems...
that money can solve.
Are there problems money can't solve?
Yes.
Like...
Like how to make someone fall in love with me.
Isn't it enough that I like you?
Who else do you want to like you?
Say it again.
I like you.
Don't say a word.
Give yourself to me... please?
No...
It's too tight.
Don't go.
Please.
I love you.
You asked for this.
Did that hurt?
A little.
Give me your hand.
Huh?
What's this?
And this is...
A New Year's gift for you.
I forgot about it earlier.
We've been together for so long.
Why are you being so cheesy?
Won't your family be upset that you came back early?
Oh. My younger sister...
Your sister?
Aren't you the only child?
What about you?
You didn't go home for New Year's.
You don't want to talk about it?
Actually, there's no special reason.
It's just...
It's just that my parents kicked me out again.
You know why.
Last summer...
I told them about our relationship.
My family is quite traditional.
How could they ever accept it?
Especially my father.
So...
So, you're all alone now.
How can you say that?
Don't I still have you?
What's wrong?
We won't ever be apart, right?
We won't break up, will we?
Of course not.
But for now...
you need to dry your hair properly.
Or else, you'll get a headache.
Since that day, Zhou Yang has been sleeping with me.
Stop working.
Come to bed.
Okay, fine.
In a moment.
No more working!
Geez, why were you so fierce just now?
Am I not allowed to be?
When my hand heals and I can paint again,
I'll find a job as an artist.
I'll support you then.
You're going to support me?
Yeah.
All right, then.
I'll wait for you to support me.
We're back at our old home.
[Shen Mo]
A graduation photo.
Isn't Zhou Yang in the graduation photo?
Who is this in the photo with me?
This isn't Zhou Yang.
Or rather...
this isn't the Zhou Yang I've been living with day and night.
Then who is this person?
If this person isn't Zhou Yang,
why did I have so much to do with him?
And if this person is Zhou Yang...
Zhou Yang.
You're back.
I'm not Zhou Yang.
And Zhou Yang isn't coming back.
Whether you keep running away,
or wake up and face reality,
it's your choice.
Zhou Yang.
Zhou Yang, come back!
Zhou Yang went abroad.
He's not coming back.
You should start a new life.
It's good that you're back.
You...
Why are you here?
Oh.
There wasn't much to do at the office,
so I came to see you.
You've started painting again.
Yes.
It's beautiful.
What's wrong?
Why are your hands so cold?
Are you too tired?
Yeah.
I know you want to paint again,
but don't push yourself too hard.
Just let it happen naturally.
Are you finished?
If you are...
Then let's go home.
Okay.
He's not Zhou Yang.
Who is this person I've been living with all this time?
Shen Mo.
It's your birthday in a few days.
How do you want to celebrate?
I never do anything special for my birthday.
There's no need to go to any trouble.
Then I'll just handle the arrangements.
He even knows my birthday.
How could he not be Zhou Yang?
But what if...
What if he's not Zhou Yang?
Why is he pretending to be Zhou Yang?
And why is he so nice to me?
What's wrong?
Are you feeling unwell?
Yeah, I feel a bit cold.
According to the report, you're recovering quite well.
Everything looks fine.
Just make sure to keep taking your medicine.
Doctor.
With my condition,
is it possible to mistake someone's identity?
Mistake someone's identity?
Like...
Like mistaking a stranger for someone very close to me?
People with severe psychological trauma
usually choose avoidance.
They'll actively try to forget certain events and people.
As for mistaking someone's identity,
it depends on the specific circumstances.
Oh.
- I understand. - All right.
Hello. The subscriber you have dialed is unavailable at the moment.
Please try again later.
Sorry, the subscriber you have dialed...
I guessed you'd be here.
Yeah.
Where else would I be?
Were you waiting for me?
Yes...
And no.
It's your birthday today.
Why didn't you come home?
I was thinking about some things.
What things?
Things from the past.
Can you tell me
what really happened in the past?
Zhou Yang.
You're not Zhou Yang.
Who are you?
You're right.
I'm not Zhou Yang.
I never was.
Since you aren't Zhou Yang, why did you pretend to be him?
Pretend to be Zhou Yang?
Weren't you the one who mistook me for him first?
Then you could have just left me alone.
You could have let me crash and burn.
Or if you wanted to be kind, you could've just dropped me at a hospital.
Why did you have to pretend to be Zhou Yang?
At first, I was afraid you'd starve to death in this house.
So, I came by occasionally to check on you.
But then I realized how stubborn and headstrong you are.
I couldn't stop worrying about you.
- And then... - And then what?
And then what happened?
Do you really not know?
Do you not know why I chose to stay?
Stop it.
It's because I love you.
Shen Mo.
A few days ago...
the doctor called me.
I already knew your memory was coming back.
So, you knew all along.
You've just been lying to me.
Actually, it's good that you've come to your senses.
You can't live in your memories forever.
Shen Mo.
Pack your things.
Come home with me.
This is my home.
But we've lived together for so long.
No.
Why not?
You're not Zhou Yang.
I'm going to wait here for Zhou Yang to return.
Zhou Yang is abroad.
And you two broke up long ago.
That's not true.
Zhou Yang and I are only temporarily apart.
Shen Mo.
Then what about me?
I only thought you were Zhou Yang.
The one I love has always been Zhou Yang.
I'm sorry.
The one you love is Zhou Yang.
I shouldn't have entered your life.
Take it back.
I intended to give it to you anyway.
There's no point in me keeping it.
From then on, he never appeared before me again.
It was as if our lives had never intersected.
[Happy Birthday] [(Address of Jinxiu Mountain Villa)]
I can't believe he gave me that house.
I believe his feelings for me are sincere.
[Jinxiu Mountain Villa]
I just want to settle things with Zhou Yang
before I think about us.
That man...
Where could he be right now?
Is he waiting for me at Jinxiu Mountain Villa?
How long will he wait?
A week?
A month?
Or even longer?
Zhou Yang.
Where are you?
Hello?
Is this Zhang?
Have you seen Zhou Yang lately?
Zhou Yang?
We haven't been in touch since graduation.
Oh, I see.
It's okay, never mind.
Sorry to bother you.
Hello?
Have you seen Zhou Yang lately?
No clue. I'm busy.
Yes, I wanted to ask you,
have you seen Zhou Yang lately?
I heard he went abroad.
Never mind then.
That person also said Zhou Yang went abroad.
Could it be that Zhou Yang and I
just ended things like that, without closure?
When I rented this house with Zhou Yang,
Zhou Yang said he found someone to handle the paperwork for us.
He said it would be more convenient.
That way, no one would find out.
[Fang Yan Zhou]
His surname really is Fang.
I remember Zhou Yang always called him "Mr. Fang".
He was an employee of the Zhou Group.
So, this is the Zhou Group's property.
Hello, sir.
How can I help you?
I'm looking for this person.
You must be talking about Secretary Fang.
His office is on the sixth floor.
You can take the elevator over there.
- Okay, thank you. - You're welcome.
Hello, Mrs. Zhou.
Hey...
Why does she look so familiar?
Hello, Mrs. Zhou.
Mrs. Zhou?
Zhou Yang's mother?
This time, I'm just teaching you a lesson.
Don't ever think of seeing Zhou Yang again.
You're not good enough for him.
Leave Zhou Yang.
Next time, it'll be your family who suffers.
I was kidnapped.
I was beaten.
My fingers were crushed.
Those weren't nightmares.
They all actually happened.
Zhou Yang.
Let's break up.
No, that wasn't the first time we met.
Before I was in the hospital,
I must have seen him before.
I remember now.
He is...
His name is Ji Ming Xuan.